Amidst the mountains, surrounded by a series of cliffs, there lies a town...
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
Wind Knights' Lot!
It was founded in the Middle Ages as a training ground for knights.
Now that it's the 19th Century, this castle fortress has been converted into a prison where the prisoners are tasked to mine for coal.
♬ 空 こぼれ落ちたふたつの星が
The townspeople have built their livelihoods around mining and the local harbor.
♬ 光と闇の水面
吸い込まれてゆく
Their current population, including prisoners, is only 517 people.
♬ 引き合うように 重なる波紋
And soon... the entire town will be wiped out!
♬～
♬ 誇りの道を往く者に
太陽の導きを
♬ 野望の果てを目指す者に
生け贄を
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
♬～
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
♬ 震えるほど心
燃え尽きるほど熱く
♬ その手から放て 鼓動
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
Quality Check:
Majora
♬ 身体 漲る勇気で
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
♬ 迷いなき覚悟に喝采を
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
♬ その血の運命 ジョジョ
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
♬～
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 5: "The Black Knights"
(ﾂｪﾍﾟﾘ)うむ…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)くっ…｡
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ)仕事をしている人々だ｡
These people are working like any other day...
This town will be all right, for now.
町は まだ 何ともないようだ｡
Moreover, I know Dio must be hiding near here!
しかし ディオは
この町のどこかに 必ずいる！
≪ パウッ！
ん？
What's the matter?
どうしました？
い… いや｡
N-Nothing...
The good Mr. Speedwagon here was being ever so persistent...
スピードワゴン君が
あまり 言うもんだからね｡
So I struck him with the intention to unlock a temporary use of the Ripple with his breathing...
一時的に 軽い波紋なら➡
作れるようにしてやろうと
思ったんだけど➡
...but I made a slight miscalculation, and my finger slipped.
ちょいと ミスった｡
指が滑っちゃった｡
Sorry... do excuse my clumsiness, Speedwagon.
いや ごめん｡
すまない！ スピードワゴン君｡
お… お前な～…｡ くっ…｡
You old coot...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)あっ｡
Mr. Zeppeli, it was just a little boy!
ツェペリさん 子供ですよ｡
子供のひったくりか｡
なかなか いい動きをしておる｡
A thieving little urchin, but that was quite the display of athleticism.
Would you two stop standing around and do something?!
２人とも
何 とろっとしてんだよ！➡
All of our money's in that bag!
あの かばんにゃあ
全財産が 入ってんだぜ！
Oh, damn it all!
ああっ ちくしょ～！
His theft and escape were flawless...
盗みが そのまま
逃走の動きになっている｡
See here...
どれ｡ あの子に 町の案内を
してもらうとするかね｡
Let's have that boy show us around town.
ピシュッ｡
ホッ ホッ｡
ホッ ホッ ホッ｡
ホホホッ ホッホッホッ…｡
ひっええ～っ!?
He's... walking on water?!
す… 水面を!?
Jojo! If the water reaches up to your knees, you aren't using the Ripple energy to its full potential!
ジョジョ 膝まで ぬれるとは
波紋ｴﾈﾙｷﾞｰの蓄積が まだ甘いな！
コォォォー｡ ふん！
ん～｡
いい音響だったぞ ジョジョ｡
That sounded good, Jojo. I can tell the Overdrive went through the entire cliff side.
オーバードライブが
確実に 伝わってゆく音だ｡
Do you think this is a good place to stand?
この辺に
立ってればいいでしょうか？
いや わしは
もう２ｍ 左と見たね｡
No, I believe another few feet to the left would be best.
２ポンド 賭けてもいいよ｡
I'd bet two quid on it!
(少年)うっ｡ わっ!?
It broke loose!
(少年)ビリッときた～！
ナイスキャッチ！
(少年)はっ｡ あ… あれ？ 何？
Nice catch!
Huh... what the...
Wait... who are you guys?
あんたたち 誰？
ん？ この少年
様子が 少し おかしいですよ｡
There's something strange about this boy...
Was my Ripple too strong?
波紋が 強すぎたかな？
いや おかしいのは
この少年だけじゃないぞ｡
No... and this boy isn't the strangest thing around here...
Take a look around you.
周りを見ろ｡
This place...
ここは!?
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)墓場!?
...is a graveyard!
あっ！
It seems we weren't the only ones to foresee our target's movements and head in for a nice catch...
どうやら おびき出されて
ナイスキャッチされたのは➡
わしらの方らしいぞ｡
その少年
催眠術を かけられとったようだ｡
That young lad was most likely under some kind of hypnosis...
Mr. Joestar, look above you!
ジョースターさん 上だ！
あっ！
んっ!?
(ﾃﾞｨｵ)日は落ちた｡
The sun has set...
...just as your lives will soon fade into darkness!
貴様の生命も 没するときだ｡
ディオ！
Dio!
は… はい上がってきた！
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ１)ぎゃぶ！
They're crawling out of the ground!
I... I've been preparing for this moment...
お… 俺は この瞬間に対する
心の準備はしてきた！
...and it's more horrifying than I ever imagined!
だが やはり
どす黒い気分になるぜ！
Just knowing that a cocky bastard like him is still alive and kicking... it makes me break out in a cold sweat!
汗が噴き出す！ あの野郎が
あんなに いい気になって➡
ぴんぴんと生きてることによ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョースター卿の愛を
血染めの裏切りで返した男｡
The wretch who repaid Lord Joestar's compassion with blood-soaked betrayal!
That... that bastard will pay!
あいつ… あいつだけは！
やつが ディオか…｡
So, that's Dio... I see...
なるほど｡ やつや ゾンビィは
太陽の下では 行動できない｡
Neither he nor his zombies could make a move while the sun was out.
So he used that hypnotized child to lure us into a battle,
assuring that the time and place would suit them.
だから
人間の子供に 催眠術をかけ➡
我々を 自分の戦いやすい
時と場所に おびき出したか？
If someone this cunning has been granted the power of the mask...
こんな こうかつなやつが
あの仮面を かぶったとは…｡
Then he must be eliminated, no matter the cost!
何としても
あの男を 消滅させねばならん！
うう…｡
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞたち)うおおお～！
騎士の死体のゾンビどもか!?
Zombies created from the corpses of knights?!
What's your name, young man?
君 名前は？
ポ… ポコ｡
P-Poco...
All right, Poco...
よし ポコ｡
僕の背に つかまっておいで｡
Get on my back, and hold on tight!
Let's go, Jojo!
行くぞ ジョジョ！
はい！
Okay!
パウッ！
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ２)ううっ｡
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ３)うあっ！
クォォー！ ズームパンチ！
Zoom Punch!
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ４)ぐへぇ｡
(ポコ)すげえ！
Amazing!
Dio Brando...
ディオ･ブランドー｡
I don't know you personally...
個人的には 貴様のことは知らん｡
だが 貴様を目覚めさせた
石仮面に対して あえて言おう｡
...but allow me to speak directly to the power of the stone mask that dwells within you.
At last, we meet again!
とうとう 会えたな｡
ヘイ ベイビー｡
そんな不安定な所で 戦う気か？
Hey baby, do you really want to fight on such shaky ground?!
Come down here!
下りてこい！
Watch your tone, insect!
図に乗るなよ｡ たかが虫けらが！
I alone sit atop the food chain...
I have become the next dominant species, ushering in a new era!
俺は 生物界の頂点｡ 未来を開く
新しい生物となった…｡
What makes you think a mere mortal could stand on equal footing with one such as myself?
人間ごときと 対等の地に
下りてゆけるか！
うっ…｡
ぬう…｡ こいつ
なんと圧倒的な 悪の大気よ！
The malevolent aura surrounding him is overwhelming!
He's able to intimidate all who stand in his way!
既に 暴帝になりつつある貫禄か!?
Once the burn on my stomach has healed,
the memory of Jojo defeating me will be completely gone...
この腹の傷を癒やせば ジョジョに
つけられた負傷は 全て完治する！
来い！ まじない師！
Come at me, magician! Let your blood help wash away my scars!
貴様の命で この傷の
くん蒸消毒してくれよう！
You monster... how many lives have you taken away in order to mend your wounds?!
貴様 一体 何人の生命を
その傷のために吸い取った？
Be honest... do you remember every crumb of bread you've ever eaten?
お前は 今まで食った
パンの枚数を覚えているのか？
くっ｡
ディオ～！
Dio!
あっ ツェペリさん！
わしがやる！
Mr. Zeppeli?!
I'll take care of him...
It's time to end this!
音を上げさせてやる！
パウ！
ああっ！
Ripple of the sun, flow through him...
流し込む 太陽の波紋
ｻﾝﾗｲﾄｲｴﾛｰｵｰﾊﾞｰﾄﾞﾗｲﾌﾞ！
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
やったぞ｡ 波紋が ディオの腕を
伝わってゆくぞ！
It's working! The Ripple is flowing into Dio's arm!
フッ｡
お… お？
Weakling, weakling!
貧弱 貧弱｡
He... he froze my arm?!
こ… 凍っている｡
こ… これは…｡
W-What is this?!
グアァァー！
な…｡
ウォォォー！
Zeppeli, was it?
ツェペリとかいうの｡
貴様のエネルギーは
血液の流れに関係あるものらしい｡
This energy you use seems to radiate from the flow of blood...
If I freeze your blood vessels, there's no path for that energy to flow through!
したがって 血管ごと凍らせれば
エネルギーは 送り出せまい｡
俺が 自分の肉体を 自在に
操れるということは知っていよう｡
I should have let you know that I have total control over my body.
I sapped the fluids from my arm after I caught your punch...
俺は 貴様の触れた腕の水分を
気化させた｡
水分は 気化するとき
同時に 熱を奪っていく｡
Without that fluid, my body was flash frozen, taking yours with it!
つまり 瞬時に凍らせたのだ｡
そして！
And now...!
はっ！
愚か者が！
Imbecile! Crushing your arm and skull will be as easy as smashing a cheap vase!
貴様の腕ごと 亀を砕くように
頭蓋骨を陥没してくれる！
Dio! I'm putting an end to your twisted schemes!
ディオ！
君の野望 僕が打ち砕く！
ディオの手
悪意の血液の流れを感じる｡
Dio's hand... I can feel pure evil flowing through his veins...
フッ 俺にとっては 褒め言葉よ｡
You flatter me...
だが しかし よくぞ
この俺の拳の動きを止めた！
And I must say, I'm impressed you managed to stop my fist.
I applaud your skill.
その成長を認めよう｡
ジョジョ！
Jojo!
Jojo...
ジョジョ 俺がお前なら➡
If I were you, I would hurry up and let go of that hand.
いつまでも
俺の手に触れてないがね｡
Take this, Dio!
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ･ﾂｪﾍﾟﾘ)食らえ ディオ！
UREEYYYY！
Wrrryyyyyy!
With your arms frozen from me sapping my fluids, your blood cannot flow.
水分気化による冷凍によって
お前らの血液は 腕を流れん！
Which means that you have no way of channeling the energy of the Ripple!
したがって 波紋エネルギーも
流れ出てこんと言ったろうが！
H-He's too powerful!
《つ… 強すぎる｡➡
The energy he wields is five times more powerful than ours combined!
やつのエネルギーの方が
わしら２人分より ５倍は強い｡➡
This is bad... I cannot allow Jojo's arm to end up like mine!
まずい｡ ジョジョの手まで わしの
右手のようになってしまう｡➡
I will not allow him to injure Jojo!
ジョジョだけは
負傷させてはいかん！》
うわっ！
ふん｡
Mr. Zeppeli!
ツェペリさん！
ハァーッ！
うわ～！
W-What just happened?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)な… なんてこった！
ああっ！
はっ｡
うわっ！
うう… すごく冷たい…｡
It's so cold...
冷たすぎて
やけどするみたいだ…｡
It's so cold, but it feels like it's burning!
My skin ripped off like I pulled my hand away from a piece of frozen metal!
凍った金属を触ったように
皮が 剥がれている｡
Old man Zeppelli's arm!
ツェペリのおっさんの腕が…｡
If we can't get the blood flowing, he'll lose his arm to frostbite!
このままじゃ
血が通わず 腐っちまう…｡
He's unstoppable...
無敵！
太陽の波紋を送り込めない｡
If there's no way to channel the Ripple of the sun, then how can we ever beat Dio?!
ディオは 倒せないのか!?
Ripple?
波紋？ 呼吸法だと？
A breathing technique?
フーフー 吹くなら…｡
If you're going to huff and puff...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)が… 岩盤が！
Th-The rocks...
...then you'd be better off using that breath to blow the trumpets for my fanfare!
この俺のために ﾌｧﾝﾌｧｰﾚでも
吹いてるのが 似合っているぞ！
Tarkus! Black Knight Bruford!
タルカス！
黒騎士 ブラフォード！
This matter isn't even worth dirtying my hands over!
もはや 俺が出るまでもない！
出てきて➡
Come forth, and play me the fanfare I deserve with their screams of agony!
こいつらに ファンファーレという
悲鳴を吹かしてみろ！
あっ｡
あっ…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
な… 何だ!? こいつらは！
W-what the hell are they?!
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)うう…｡
Poco! Hide somewhere safe!
ポコ！ 隠れているんだ！
う… うん！
16世紀 エリザベス１世に
処刑された 悲運の女王➡
These fearsome knights served the most unfortunate Mary Stuart.
They were executed with Mary at the hands of Elizabeth I!
メアリー･スチュアートに仕えた
どう猛な騎士たちよ｡
Clean up this mess.
後始末！ この虫けらどもの駆除は
お前たち ２人に任せるぞ！
The two of you, do whatever is necessary to stamp out these insects.
好きにしろ！
指１本で
岩を 持ち上げただけじゃなく➡
He didn't just hold up that rock with one finger... he shattered it, too!
壊しやがった！
むっ！
Those zombies...
あのゾンビども！
２人とも ジョジョへ！
They're headed towards Jojo!
It's no good... he can't win when he's outnumbered!
む… 無理だ｡ ２対１では勝てん｡
If only the blood were still flowing in my arm...
この腕に 血液さえ通えば…｡
通ったら どうなる？
If it were, what could you do?
呼吸法で 少しは 傷を癒やせる｡
I could use a breathing technique to heal my wounds...
There must be some way for me to thaw my arm!
何とか
この腕を溶かす方法はないか…｡
Old man Zeppeli, you just need to thaw out your arm, right?!
ツェペリのおっさんよ！
溶かせばいいんだな？
その凍った腕をよ！
な… 何をする気だ!?
D-Do you have something in mind?!
Something... like this!
これなら どうだ～!?
Speedwagon!
スピードワゴン君！
The men of the arctic recovered from frostbite by warming their limbs with the flesh from a freshly killed seal!
極寒地に住むやつらはよ
凍傷にかかったとき➡
アザラシの体内に入って
治していたぜ｡
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)ふん！
Zoom Punch!
ズームパンチ！
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)貴様の血を頂くぜ！
Your blood belongs to me now!
ああっ｡
うっ…｡
す… 吸い取っているのか!?
H-He's draining my blood?!
S-Speedwagon... what are you...
スピードワゴン…
君ってやつは…｡
俺はよ
あんたや ジョースターさんの➡
I didn't come all this way just to be a bother for you and Mr. Joestar!
足手まといになるために
付いてきたんじゃあねえぜ！
髪で吸血するなら
逆に この髪の毛から➡
If he can drain blood through his hair,
then that means I can send a Ripple through it!
波紋を送り込んでやる！
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
サンライトイエロー
オーバードライブ！
I-I can't generate a Ripple?!
はっ 波紋ができない！
血液を 吸い取られているから
波紋が弱いのか!?
Or is the Ripple weak because of all the blood I've lost?!
I underestimated you...
わしは 君を軽んじておった…｡
I expected you to run when things started to get out of hand...
いざというとき
逃げ出す男だと…｡
すまなかった…｡
I'm sorry I doubted you...
You can thank me after we make it through this fight, old man!
礼は 戦いが終わって
生き延びてから言えってんだ｡
あ… ああ…｡
は… 早く 傷を癒やし
戦う状態にせねば！
I-I have to heal as fast as I can to rejoin the battle!
俺の 氷のやけどの痛みも
忘れてしまうほどの戦慄！
I'm too terrified to even feel the pain from the frostbite forming on my chest...
That sword is so big, it dwarfs Mr. Joestar's 6'4" body!
ジョースターさんの
195cmの体が➡
小さく見えるほどの
ビッグサーベル！➡
得体の知れぬ黒髪！
それに あの２人の面構え！➡
That mysterious black hair... and the expressions on their faces!
There's something about those two...
何かを秘めている！
多くの人間を見てきた 俺には➡
With all that I've seen in my life, I can tell there's something overwhelming about these two!
その圧倒的な何かを 感じる！
Every true Englishman knows the names of these legendary knights...
英国人なら 誰もが知る伝説の騎士
タルカスとブラフォード｡
Tarkus and Bruford!
I can make history itself serve me!
俺は
歴史さえも しもべにできる！
Long ago, in the year 1565...
〈今は昔 1565年ごろ➡
Two queens were at odds for the throne of England.
王位継承を争った
２人の女王がいた｡➡
One of them was Queen Elizabeth I...
１人は 女王 エリザベス１世｡➡
The other was the beautiful 23 year-old Mary Stewart.
もう１人は 美貌の23歳
メアリー･スチュアート｡➡
勇者 タルカスと
黒騎士 ブラフォードは➡
The hero, Tarkus, and the Black Knight, Bruford, were both loyal to Mary.
メアリーの
忠実なる家来だった｡➡
These men, orphaned and homeless as a result of the war,
were taken in by Mary's warm hospitality.
戦で 親兄弟を失い
天涯孤独だった２人を➡
温かく 包み込んでくれる
メアリー｡➡
Even the most powerful of men will seek comfort for their soul.
どんなに強い男でも
心に安らぎを求める…｡➡
In Mary's presence, they felt something far more profound than love.
恋ではなく
もっと 大きなものに｡➡
メアリーには
その魅力があった｡➡
The two were prepared to sacrifice their lives for Mary's sake.
２人は 命を
投げ出してもよいとするほどの➡
忠誠を 心に誓っていた｡➡
Mary's husband, Lord Darnley, met an untimely demise!
ところが あるとき
メアリーの夫 ダーンリーが➡
不慮の死に見舞われる｡➡
Elizabeth saw this an opportunity, casting suspicion on Mary for the death of her husband!
そこに目をつけた エリザベスは
夫殺しの容疑を➡
メアリーにかけたのだ｡➡
The people turned against Mary, and as a result she was captured and imprisoned.
国中が メアリーの敵に回った｡➡
そして メアリーは捕らえられ
幽閉されてしまう｡➡
タルカスと ブラフォードは
メアリーを救うため戦い続けた｡➡
Tarkus and Bruford battled endlessly to rescue Mary...
With few other options to choose from,
Elizabeth approached the knights with an offer.
この２人に手を焼いた
エリザベスは 取引を持ちかける〉
"If the two of you surrender at once, I shall spare Mary's life."
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)
《２人とも 直ちに自首せよ！➡
そうすれば
メアリーの命だけは 助けよう｡》
We cannot refuse such an offer...
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)《我々に
この要求 断れるはずなし！》
We accept with no regret.
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)《悔いはなし！》
The two knights were captured... and then executed...
〈２人は 捕らえられた｡➡
そして 処刑される〉
Let me tell you one last thing before you die...
(処刑人)《冥土の土産に
教えてやるぜ｡➡
Mary is already dead!
メアリーは 既に死んだよ！➡
You idiots were tricked!
貴様らは だまされたんだよ｡➡
Look... see that heap of trash over there?
ほ～れ！ あそこに
ごみのように 転がっとるやつ｡➡
あれが メアリーさ》
That's your precious Mary!
《ああっ！ ああ…｡➡
うおおおおおおお‼》
Damn you, Elizabeth!
《おのれ エリザベス！➡
How... How dare you betray our agreement!
よくも… よくも
裏切ってくれたな～‼》
You've brought a curse upon yourself! Upon you and all your kin!
《この恨み！ 呪ってやる！➡
てめえらの子孫末代に
至るまで…》
Beyond death itself, we curse you!
《呪い抜いてやる～‼》
〈２人は こうして処刑された｡➡
Thus, they were executed.
It was said that Tarkus' neck, wrought tense from rage,
broke many an executioner's axe before fully giving way.
タルカスは
その筋肉が 怒りのため 硬直し➡
首を切り落とすのに 処刑人は
何本もの斧を折ったという｡➡
ブラフォードは その長髪が
処刑人の足に絡みつき➡
Bruford supposedly sunk his teeth into the leg of his executioner,
tearing off a chunk of his flesh before finally submitting to death.
肉まで食い込んで
死んでいったという〉
そして 俺は！
I found myself quite enchanted by their savagery!
この２人の 鳥肌 立つような
妄執が 気に入った！
I dug up the graves of those two heroes who died cursing humanity, and I chose to give them new life! It was all thanks to me, Dio!
人を恨み 世を呪い 死んでいった
伝説の勇者の墓を暴き➡
生命を与えたのは このディオ！
I turned them into machines of vengeance that the devil himself would fear!
２人を 悪魔も ぶっ飛ぶ
復しゅう鬼に つくりあげたぜ！
Wrryyy... We have sworn loyalty to Master Dio!
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)UREEYYY！
我らは ディオ様に忠誠を誓った！
We will spread destruction across the earth!
この世を滅亡させてやる！
どいつもこいつも 皆殺しだ！
Every last one of you will die!
あ… 圧倒的な怨念だ！
怨念だけが 増大してる！
Th-That thirst for revenge... It made their bodies grow with their hate!
グワッ！
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)グワーッ！
Dio has turned these heroes into monsters!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ディオは 英雄を魔物に変えた！➡
Is there any way we can defeat these beasts?!
勝てるのか!?
この すさまじい妄執に!?
コォォォー｡
In my left hand... I channel the Ripple of fire!
左手にためる 炎の波紋｡
Scarlet Overdrive!
スカーレットオーバードライブ！
あっ！
な… なんと!?
A-Amazing!
I forgot... there's something that drives Mr. Joestar to grow as well!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)わ… 忘れていた！➡
ジョースターさんにも
背負っているものがある！➡
It's his love for his late father, his hope for a bright future...
亡き父への思いと
未来への希望が！➡
And for the hopes of us all!
俺たちの希望が！
この小僧 少しはやるな｡
This boy seems like he has some potential...
300年ぶりの ｳｫｰﾐﾝｸﾞｱｯﾌﾟにゃ
ちょうどいい相手だ！
He'll make a passable warm-up after 300 years of slumber!
あっ｡
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ１)GOOORRUUUU！➡
この野郎を食うのは 俺だぜ～！
軟骨がうめ～んだよ｡ 軟骨が～！
I'm gonna swallow you whole!
I bet your cartilage is scrumptious!
Another zombie?!
新手のゾンビ！
Underlings like you... should know your place!
雑魚は 出てくるんじゃあない｡
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ１)きゃん！
《な… なんて速さだ！》
W-What speed!
Master Dio!
ディオ様 この若者
なかなか 根性の据わった男｡➡
I am impressed with the boldness that this young man displays!
I, Bruford, ask you to grant me the honor of bringing death upon him!
このブラフォードに
この者の 生命の幕を➡
引かせていただきたい！
好きにしろ｡
Do as you like.
Tarkus! Leave us be.
タルカス！ 手出し無用｡
The Black Knight, Bruford... what savage power!
黒騎士 ブラフォード
なんと 猛然たるパワー｡
しかも 残酷性 十分！
And such ruthlessness, as well!
His confidence and strength radiate from him like an aura!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)全身から みなぎる
自分の能力と➡
戦闘への 誇り高き自信！
奇妙な気分だ…｡ 学校で習った
黒騎士 ブラフォードが➡
It's surreal... The very same Bruford the Black Knight that we learned about in school...
僕の前へ
怨念を抱えて 向かってくる｡
Now he stands before me, ready to unleash his vengeful rage!
I have to steady my breath!
呼吸を整えろ！
Relax my muscles!
筋肉を リラックスさせろ！
ふんっ URYYAAAHHHH！
W-What?!
な… 何だ!?
両腕を 後ろへ回しているぞ！
He has both arms behind his back! How will I know which one he's attacking with?!
どっちの腕で攻撃してくる？
それとも 足か!?
Or will he use his legs?!
In a shocking twist, he used his hair!
〈意外！ それは 髪の毛！〉
D-Damn--!
し… しまっ…｡
うわ～！ あっ あっ！
ほう 勘のいいやつ｡
You have impressive reflexes...
Few would be able to dodge my Dance Macabre Hair in time...
俺の ダンス･マカブヘアーに
気付くとは…｡ 面白い！
Intriguing!
ああ～！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョースターさん！
Mr. Joestar!
This is bad... He won't be able to breathe underwater!
まずいぞ！
水中では 呼吸ができない｡
Which means he won't be able to use the Ripple!
つまり 波紋法ができない！
すぐ 助けに行かないと！
We have to do something!
うわっ！
タ… タルカス！
T-Tarkus!
Damn it... we can't get to Mr. Joestar with him in the way!
さ… 最悪！ ジョースターさんを
救いに行けない！
フッ…｡
The battle is already won. Bruford has an overwhelming advantage in water.
《勝負はついたな｡
水中は ブラフォードの独壇場》
There is no need for the mighty Dio to remain here!
このディオ！
もう この場にいる必要なし！➡
The time has come for me to transform the people of Wind Knights' Lot into an army of zombies!
いよいよ ｳｲﾝﾄﾞﾅｲﾂ･ﾛｯﾄの町
住民 全員を ゾンビにする！
In one more night, the zombies will spread,
and then... they will consume all of England!
あと 一昼夜のうちに！
そして この町から ゾンビが
イギリス中に広がるだろう！
《こ… 呼吸が…｡
波紋をつくるために 欲しい！➡
One breath...
Just one breath, and I can use the Ripple!
たった 一呼吸！》
Now, our battle will commence underwater!
さあ 水面まで泳げよ｡
お前には 呼吸のハンデがあり➡
Your lack of breath is your handicap,
while mine is the heavy armor weighing me down.
俺には この かっちゅうの重さの
ハンデがある！
剣は使わん！
これは 勇者としての決闘だ！
I will not use my sword...
This shall be a battle between true warriors!
ぐ… ぐぁ…｡
Now, try and defeat me before you drown!
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)さあ！ 溺れ死なんうちに
何とかしてみろ！
《この距離
彼より先に 水面に出れるか!?➡
Can I reach the surface before he closes the gap between us?!
Do I stand a chance to win?!
僕に 勝機は…》
ガ… ガゴボッ…｡
〈断末魔の一瞬｡ ジョジョの
精神内に潜む 爆発力が➡
On the brink of defeat, the explosive power within Jojo brought forth a risky last-ditch idea!
とてつもない冒険を生んだ｡➡
普通の人間は
追い詰められ 息が苦しければ➡
The average person would only think to swim to the surface as they struggle for breath.
水面に出ようとばかり考える｡
だが ジョジョは違った！➡
However, Jojo did not!
He did the exact opposite... He dove even deeper!
逆に なんと！
さらに 湖底へ潜った！〉
W-What is he doing?!
な… 何だ？ こいつ｡
What? Danny took hold of your toy gun and won't let go?
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
《何？ ダニーが おもちゃの
鉄砲をくわえて 離さない？➡
That's because you're trying to force him to give it back.
それは 無理やり
引き離そうとするからだよ｡➡
Instead, try letting him think that you're giving it to him.
逆に考えるんだ｡
｢あげちゃってもいいさ｣と》
Wind Knights' Lot is a coal mining town!
《ウインドナイツ･ロットは
石炭の採れる土地｡➡
つまり
昔 地盤沈下があったということ》
That means that the earth around here has been excavated and filled in countless times!
あ… あった！
There!
《つまり 水没した岩の隙間に
空気があるはず！➡
There should be pockets of air trapped beneath these rocks!
That's it!
これだ！ 一呼吸あれば！➡
All I need is a single breath!
I can feel it... The beat of my pulse pounding!
刻むぞ 血液のビート！》
H-He's...
こ… こいつ！
It seems you're the one at a disadvantage fighting underwater!
《水中での戦いが
不利になったのは 貴様の方だ！➡
Because, you see... the Ripple is naturally channeled through water!
たやすいぞ！
波紋が 水中を伝わるのは！》
This is it! Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
《水中のための…➡
ターコイズブルー
オーバードライブ‼》
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ You spend the day away
We spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley... hey!
In and around the lake
♬ In and around the lake
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
there with you
♬～
Next Episode
You're pathetic, Bruford!
I am an elite slaughterer!
This pain is nothing!
Yours is a destiny of bloodshed.
Life force Magnetism Overdrive!
Episode 6:
"Courage of Tomorrow"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
見苦しいぜ ブラフォード！
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)だが 俺は
殺りくのエリートを目指し…｡
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)これしきの痛み！
(ﾄﾝﾍﾟﾃｨ)死への宿命を
背負うことになるぞ｡
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ･ﾂｪﾍﾟﾘ)
生命磁気へのオーバードライブ！